Hello Hello Friends Welcome to Smart
Wealth Advisors Here are the
results of Siddence Life Insurance Again disclaimer
this is a good
vegetable stock in my portfolio and this is my long term long term
stock
in my portfolio now when I one winner is a long
term means that minimum of Scientific
Advisor 19 2012 result share subscribe
and today how much is the close then 50 okay and
see this so now let's go ahead and
show a little comparison or I will go to the screen with this I do
n't know in the screen I had approved that it happened so let's come
here through this only
come through life and we have here
now so good I think this uploads result
that not us Aishwarya got one and a half from Bigg Boss 302
but properties Nirodh 205 crore
okay now I was going to show that
HDFC Cup Rajshree Ojha was 263 crore
here and send this and don't then
profit better from them okay even then  That's why
we see all this, its
market would have been double the market now,
its double subscribe and ko, okay, so let
's make its balance a little bigger, it was done
by Jumet, the
boy who got it,
so hop, you will also know well,
I will read its balance sheet here a little bit, the
price of any insurance company is a little bit
tricky, so I will not go
directly here, we will see here December 31st,
so we will directly come in this
Jugaad comparison, you will have to see, then you will
see from quarter to quarter and this is yours, so there is
cross like improvement on almost every parameter,
okay, so its expenses are very
much in control
system management, that's why I have gym control,
okay, so mainly their
expenses are the same, that is the specialty of these companies,
okay, but long term and long term
ten loop control system, so
people do
not stay online due to advertising and the reaction is that
after that, in a way, then a
little here, now why do any companies give
any company their,  It takes time to
make a snort, take a selfie,
people, the secretary of the license scheme, Everything
in India 332 company, believe it, they have total
insurance, but
building a brand is a huge barrier reef, which is very
easy, and then we put in the profit
loss book 300 crores, we gave one crore,
here the answer is 3 to 5 crores profit,
okay, this is theirs,
now what will we do in this, we will not go into this,
we will come to Delhi again, but feel
better picture of keywords opening to
the company, okay, let's go to Suzanne Roshan and make
it a little smaller, the
treatment is clear, you should
also sleep on the torch light, this is of no use to us, let's move ahead,
this is a quarter inch solvency amount,
services percentage, subscribe as
much as you want, then you
can do everything, the specialty of ghee is balance ghee, not only
this, it is doing very well in profit margin,
now
that there has been a lot of decline in happiness,
okay, so it means hotel, resort, Suez loop, if you
go to other places then persistence one
Again very important Om gold standard
so there is improvement in both purchases something like
this very nice subscribe and there is
some rate reduction for taking this policy
okay let's see where it is
today you will see in many ways recently
their juice came in unity plan
this is within the current pension plans and
both of them again in the meantime life
is the boys in 21 seats but they will start
so if you liked the video then
subscribe to so how and subscribe do
not forget to subscribe to the channel and
subscribe and whatever amount is there the
customer has to return
and if there is any benefit then there is an option so
whatever is left then subscribe for round-round *
so that the money can be withdrawn in it, it
is very strong and like till the time
this means in business
till that a
jhal so those who have growth in the market pimp
like good in everything their anger has come
in rallies
battery saving is very high means
constipation is very high it is going to reduce  There is
immediate production on this screen,
okay, so this is a little weak, we
can do it, they will have to bill up there, okay, okay, the
meaning of respect energy,
where does it come from, but only from their
distribution, okay, now in this quarter,
RBL Bank, this small finance bank,
their distribution pipeline is on the phone, so
weekly it will automatically improve growth
seats, generally these people sell unification of clans,
otherwise Sherlyn's which
gives Pushp with Baghwa and its agency is also very,
it is of 90, so it is very much,
now the new topic has increased, IDBI Bank is
with Grindr with Edison, friend, bill
Mangroo is big, talk idea, new branches have increased for
them to sell, it happened,
I still still, if you see Manika, there is a
lot of difference between the agency and bank balance, the
more it gradually becomes agency and bangal scam, the better it is
because
less commission has to be paid in the test, okay, so the
rest of the net production business,
retail continues to dominate  That's good
group prince, commissions are less in it
and it is of middle order time only, so the
more dominant the retail the
better it is, the best is presidency, they have
very good influence persistence and
Das Kabir was looking for it to come from close by,
means whoever is coming back then
subscribe button Idea you should subscribe so
subscribe subscribe absolutely
on your track okay now subscribe to it, the
amount of money that you are making was waste, you will keep
making almost two, okay, at whatever time the
jagat investment increased or decreased, their
body was very good after all this time the
market becomes good okay that those who do
not but when Meghnad total 22 crore
units then those who invest
on the strength of their money, thank you very much, do
not forget to subscribe to the channel so that two